ourbestbites.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy | Our Best Bites

## **Our Best Bites  respects your privacy.**

Our Best Bites, LLC operates www.OurBestBites.com and may operate other websites. It is Our Best Bites’ policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites, and to use responsible practices in the collection, maintenance and use of your personal information.

When you use any website operated by Our Best Bites, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and Our Best Bites will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of any website of Our Best Bites.

 **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Our Best Bites collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. We may store information about the type of browser you are using, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the referring site. Our Best Bites’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Our Best Bites’ visitors use its website. From time to time, Our Best Bites may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Our Best Bites also collects potentially personally-identifying information like IP addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on www.Our BestBites.com blogs/sites. Our Best Bites only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

 **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Our Best Bites’ websites choose to interact with Our Best Bites in ways that require Our Best Bites to gather personally-identifying information. In general, you can visit our Website without telling us who you are or sharing any Personally Identifiable Information.  
The amount and type of information that Our Best Bites gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at www.OurBestBites.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Our Best Bites are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required for us or our service providers to process those transactions. In each case, Our Best Bites collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Our Best Bites.

Our Best Bites does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **Application of United States Laws**

The websites of Our Best Bites is based on computers located in the United States. Your Personally Identifiable Information will be used and stored in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may differ from the level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as in Mexico, Canada and the European Union.

 **Aggregated Statistics**

Our Best Bites may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Our Best Bites may display this information publicly or provide it to others. We may analyze aggregated anonymous information on the pages visited by our users to make our Website more accessible and useful. Further, we may share this data with third parties, usually to provide services for Our Best Bites associated with the maintenance of its websites, or its service providers. However, Our Best Bites does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

 **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Our Best Bites discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Our Best Bites’ behalf or to provide services available at Our Best Bites’ websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Our Best Bites’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Our Best Bites will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Our Best Bites discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Our Best Bites believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Our Best Bites, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of any Our Best Bites website and have supplied your email address, Our Best Bites may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Our Best Bites and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Our Best Bites takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

Our Best Bites may use cookies (a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns), Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a website that monitors usage), and other similar technologies to improve the quality of its websites and to better target and analyze consumer behavior with the goal of providing better and more relevant advertising. Additionally, some of our service providers may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. Our cookie does not include your name or anything personal to you. It simply tells us that we have encountered your computer at some prior point. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. Our Best Bites visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Our Best Bites’ websites, with the drawback that certain features of Our Best Bites’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **Service Providers**

Our Best Bites may share personally identifiable Information with its service providers that help it provide the services that you request (“Service Providers”). For example, Our Best Bites may contract with service providers to provide certain services, such as credit card processing, advertising, analytics tools, data management services, Web hosting, and Web development. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services, however, each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

 **Third Party Websites**

The websites of Our Best Bites may contain links to websites or content operated and maintained by third parties. Our Best Bites does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our practices. If you click on a link or an advertisement, the privacy policy of the website to which you link will govern the collection and use of your information by that website’s operator(s). You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before disclosing any information to the website.

 **Business Transfers**

If Our Best Bites, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Our Best Bites goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Our Best Bites may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

 **Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Our Best Bites and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or other service providers.

 **Security**

Our Best Bites employs commercially reasonable security measures to reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. However, Our Best Bites cannot and do not guarantee that these measures will be sufficient to protect against all efforts to gain unauthorized access to that information.

 **Children’s Privacy**

Our Best Bites are committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). Our Website is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we receive personally identifiable information that we discover was provided by a child under the age of 13, we will promptly destroy such information. Schools and parents should supervise their children’s online activities and consider the use of other means to provide a child-friendly, online environment.  
Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Our Best Bites may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Our Best Bites’ sole discretion. Our Best Bites encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

For any other information email general@ourbestbites.com.
